I'm still a fan even though I was salty
Hate to see you with some other broad, know you happy
Hate to see you happy if I'm not the one driving
I'm so mature, I'm so mature
I'm so mature.
I'm so mature, I got me a therapist to tell me there's other men
I don't want none, I just want you
If I can't have you, no one should
I might
Not the best idea (idea)
His new girlfriend's next, how'd I get here?
I might kill my ex, not the best idea
I still love him though (I do)
Rather be in jail than alone
I get the sense that it's a lost cause
I get the sense that you might really love her
This text gon' be evidence, this text is evidence
The sex is evidence.
I tried to ration with you, no murders or crimes of passion, but damn
Now I'm in the basement, planning home invasion
But damn.
You was out of reach
You was at the farmer's market with your perfect peach
Now I'm in the basement.
Planting on my beige.
Now you laying face-down, got me singing over a beat
Got me saying all about a piece.
I'm so mature.
I'm so mature, I got me a therapist to tell me there's other men
I don't want none, I just want you
If I can't have you, no one will
I might kill my ex, not the best idea
I might get my ex.
Not the best idea.
His new girlfriend's next, how'd I get here?
How'd I get here?
I just killed my ex (my ex)
I might kill my ex, I still love him though
Rather be in jail than alone
I did it all for love (love)
I did it all on no drugs (drugs)
I did all of this sober
I did it all for us, oh
I did it all for love (love)
I did all of this sober
I did all of this on no drugs (drugs)
I did it all for us all.
I did it all for love.
I did it all on no drugs.
I did it all for us all.
Uh, I just killed my ex (my ex)
Not the best idea.
Killed his girlfriend next, how'd I get here? (He left me no choice)
How'd I get here?
I just killed my ex.
I might kill my ex, I still love him though
Rather be in Hell than alone
I did it all for love.
I did it all for us all.